<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arnav Sood</title>
    <link>http://arnavsood.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arnav Sood</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:05:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://arnavsood.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>consulting</title>
      <link>http://arnavsood.com/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:05:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arnavsood.com/consulting/</guid>
      <description>I consult on projects that require skill with computation or math.
For rates and availability, please write to consulting@arnavsood.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quotes</title>
      <link>http://arnavsood.com/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arnavsood.com/quotes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We have not found any authority for the proposition that the world is a community&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
 Internal Revenue Service, denying a nonprofit application from an open-source software group.
 &amp;ldquo;I watch the government and report the facts, that is all I do.&amp;rdquo;
 Will Rogers, one of America&amp;rsquo;s greatest comedians.
 &amp;ldquo;Ships that pass in the night, and speak each other in passing, Only a signal shown and a distant voice in the darkness; So on the ocean of life, we pass and speak one another, Only a look and a voice, then darkness again and a silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>writing</title>
      <link>http://arnavsood.com/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 21:25:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arnavsood.com/writing/</guid>
      <description> Here are some things I&amp;rsquo;ve written.
Non-Fiction  &amp;ldquo;Bounded Rationality&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; Blanket Sea. Pushcart Prize nominee.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links</title>
      <link>http://arnavsood.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:28:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arnavsood.com/links/</guid>
      <description>Some things I think are worth sharing.
 WIPP: How to warn people 10000 years from now about radioactive waste. Sylvia Jacobson: Was confined to a skyjacked plane for a week, and wrote a paper about it. Ken Liu: State Change (short story). 129 Cars: This American Life (WBEZ Chicago) spends a month at a car dealership.   The Glass Room: A digital art exhibit by Mozilla, focused on examining issues of data and privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://arnavsood.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 13:29:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arnavsood.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Predoctoral Fellow in Economics at UBC, working primarily with Jesse Perla on computational macro.
I&amp;rsquo;m also part of the team at QuantEcon, where I work on Julia and infrastructure projects.
My email&amp;rsquo;s arnav.sood@ubc.ca. If you&amp;rsquo;re on campus, my office is in the Iona building.
If you prefer to communicate securely, here&amp;rsquo;s my PGP public key.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>